

ABOUT ME

I am Sneha Dhumal, college student currently studying in Third Year-Bachelor's in Computer Engineering, at Atharva College of Engineering.

I am into Web designing, Machine Learning, and a Cloud Enthusiast. Experienced in web designing and front-end development. **Experienced with Microsoft** products such as PowerApps,

SharePoint, PowerBI, Power Automate.

SKILLS

HTML & CSS **JAVASCRIPT PYTHON** MYSQL PHP MICROSOFT POWERAPPS MICROSOFT SHAREPOINT ONLINE MICROSOFT POWERAUTOMATE

CONTACT



+91-9594870618



Mumbai



snehakrishnadhumal@gmail.com

SNEHA DHUMAL

FRESHER

EDUCATION

Atharva College of Engineering

2019-2023

CGPA: 9.58 (till SEM V)

Thakur College of Science and Commerce

2017-2019

Percentage: 84.4%

WORK EXPERIENCE

KwebMaker PVT LTD [Intern]

December 2021- January 2022 Worked as Front-End Developer

Maverics Technologies [Intern]

July 2021 - October 2021

Worked with Microsoft Products and built an application using them

EXTRA CURRICULAM

Participated with the team in the AI Hackathon IIT conducted by Kaggle and secured 8th position

Participated with the team in AET ENGENIUS an intercollege fest, and secured 2nd position

INTEREST IN

Python Programming: Building GUI applications using PYQT5. Styling webpages using CSS.

Web Development

AI /ML/BI

Cloud Technologies